<idea-plugin>
  <id>com.elliotwaite.cyberpunk_theme</id>
  <name>Cyberpunk Theme</name>
  <version>1.1.2</version>
  <vendor email="elliot@elliotwaite.com" url="https://github.com/elliotwaite/jetbrains-cyberpunk-theme">Elliot Waite</vendor>

  <description><![CDATA[
      A theme inspired by the UI colors in Cyberpunk 2077.<br />
      <br />
      To match the font in the plugin's <a href="https://plugins.jetbrains.com/plugin/15563-cyberpunk-theme">screenshots</a>:<br />
      <ul>
          <li>Preferences > Editor > Font > Font: <b>Source Code Pro</b> (downloadable <a href="https://fonts.google.com/specimen/Source+Code+Pro">here</a>)</li>
          <li>Preferences > Appearance & Behavior > Appearance > Antialiasing > IDE: <b>Greyscale</b></li>
          <li>Preferences > Appearance & Behavior > Appearance > Antialiasing > Editor: <b>Greyscale</b></li>
      </ul>
      <br />
      To report a bug or make a suggestion, open an issue on <a href="https://github.com/elliotwaite/jetbrains-cyberpunk-theme">GitHub</a>.<br />
      <br />
      This theme is open source under the <a href="https://github.com/elliotwaite/jetbrains-cyberpunk-theme/blob/master/LICENSE">MIT license</a>.<br/>
    ]]></description>

  <change-notes><![CDATA[
      <b>1.1.2</b>
      <ul>
        <li>
          This change makes it so that selected files in the file browser will
          still show as selected (they will have a light grey background color)
          even when the file browser panel is not focused. This also applies to
          any other tree views other than the file browser. See here for more
          details:
          https://github.com/elliotwaite/jetbrains-cyberpunk-theme/pull/6.
        </li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.1.1</b>
      <ul>
        <li>
          The default code style for Rust adds an underline to mutable
          variable. This update changes the color of that underline from its
          default light pink color to a gray.
        </li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.1.0</b>
      <ul>
        <li>
          In this update, most of the background colors have been shifted
          slightly darker and other changes were made to make it compatible
          with JetBrain's new UI. Going forward, this theme will be mainly
          tested using the new UI, but it should still work well with the
          legacy UI (non-new UI). If you notice anything that looks off when
          using the legacy UI, please let me know on GitHub.
        </li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.12</b>
      <ul>
        <li>
          Updated the context menu's background color to be a slightly darker
          grey.
        </li>
        <li>
          Changed the context menu selected item's background color from blue
          to a grey that is slightly lighter than the background.
        </li>
        <li>
          The following elements were using non-theme grey colors, so they were
          slightly adjusted to use grey colors from the theme's palette:
          ERROR_HINT, INFORMATION_HINT, LOOKUP_COLOR, CODE_LENS_BORDER_COLOR
        </li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.11</b>
      <ul>
        <li>
          Changed the TODO stripe mark color from red to dark grey. This stripe
          mark is shown in the right scrollbar to identify TODO comments. The
          dark grey color better reflects that it's a TODO comment and not
          an error.
        </li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.10</b>
      <ul>
        <li>Changed class name color from white to green.</li>
        <li>Changed interface name color from white to green.</li>
        <li>Changed JavaScript global variable color from white to orange.</li>
        <li>Changed TypeScript narrowed type background color from grey to none.</li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.9</b>
      <ul>
          <li>Updated button colors.</li>
          <li>Updated welcome screen background colors.</li>
          <li>Updated mnemonic bookmark button colors.</li>
          <li>Several syntax color updates.</li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.8</b>
      <ul>
          <li>Updated the syntax colors for web related files (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, etc.).</li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.7</b>
      <ul>
          <li>Fixed the "List > selectionInactiveBackground" color.</li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.6</b>
      <ul>
          <li>Expanded the compatibility range to include all current and future EAP versions.</li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.5</b>
      <ul>
          <li>Updated the colors for user-defined file types.</li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.4</b>
      <ul>
          <li>Updated the PHP syntax colors.</li>
      </ul>
      <b>1.0.3</b>
      <ul>
          <li>Updated the plugin icon.</li>
      </ul>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <!-- please see https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/build-number-ranges.html for description -->
  <idea-version since-build="173.0"/>
  <!-- <idea-version since-build="223"/> -->

  <!-- please see https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-compatibility.html
       on how to target different products -->
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <!-- Add your extensions here -->
    <themeProvider id="3f316286-64a8-421b-91ae-21b0dfde096d" path="/cyberpunk_theme.theme.json"/>
  </extensions>

  <actions>
    <!-- Add your actions here -->
  </actions>

</idea-plugin>